[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 27?",
      "correctAnswer": "729",
      "options": [
        "734",
        "731",
        "729",
        "727"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "14",
        "9",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 29?",
      "correctAnswer": "841",
      "options": [
        "841",
        "843",
        "839",
        "846"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "196",
      "options": [
        "194",
        "198",
        "201",
        "196"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "7",
        "14",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 12?",
      "correctAnswer": "144",
      "options": [
        "142",
        "146",
        "149",
        "144"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "16",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "18",
        "16",
        "21"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 23?",
      "correctAnswer": "529",
      "options": [
        "534",
        "527",
        "529",
        "531"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "49",
      "options": [
        "49",
        "47",
        "51",
        "54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "441",
      "options": [
        "443",
        "441",
        "439",
        "446"
      ]
    }
]